We can pick some up on the way home.
Your attention, please.
A deadly virus has been unleashed to punish humanity for foolishness.
There is no cure.
Your last night is on the way home.
Mika, I don't think she's breathing.
Keep them over there, you!
Director, can you hear me?
However, we have chosen to spare the young.
This virus will not affect anyone 13 or younger.
The direct unit of the third progenitor, Kul Temesh, is currently collecting the children of this district.
From this day forward, we shall be under our protection.
Captain Chad, pull us!
Help us!
A very simple idea, having a safer lifeGB interned by heart,
the beginning of our socials was организued,
but we'll see if this will really last panel for us.
It would be...
While it might be announcing an opportunity
to join the world for us,
the witness said to pasa combat inevitably.
Can you hold others can't be used by words?
Gotta be loud,
a very OFTRA lango.
Let's go.
Who's next?
Yuichiro Hyakuya.
Okay, next.
Mikayla Hyakuya.
Let's go.
Stop wasting it.
Do you want to get sick?
It's nasty.
I won't drink this crap.
You need to quit being so picky.
And you need to quit doing what the Fangs tell you.
I don't think it's all that bad, to be honest.
Seriously?
At least we're alive.
And more importantly, we get to live with our family.
Don't you think that's enough?
I'm not their livestock.
It's like talking to a wall with you.
That stubborn streak won't keep them away from your neck.
Hey!
You know?
Don't!
Apologize!
Do it or else!
Please, sir.
Ignore him.
You see, he's just a harmless moron.
What?
I'll take care of him.
I swear this won't happen again.
Can it, Mika?
I'm in the middle of kicking this guy's ass!
What's going on here?
No hood.
Is he a noble?
Lord Farid!
Ah, young Mika.
What's all the fuss about?
Oh, nothing.
Just one of my family members causing trouble again.
That must be so stressful.
Poor Mika.
I know.
Why don't you come by my mansion again tonight?
I would like that.
As would I, dear boy.
You have such sweet blood.
You're always welcome.
And will the troublemaker be joining us?
Huh?
Like hell, I...
Oh, I don't know if that's a good idea.
He's shy.
What a shame.
Maybe next time.
Hm.
You just had to go and butt in, didn't you?
I had that parasite right where I wanted him.
You can't really believe that.
Fess up.
You know we don't have a prayer against the vampires.
They're too strong for us.
We won't know for sure till we give it a try.
Yeah, yeah.
You keep fooling yourself.
Look.
I get that you're angry, but you need to be more careful, okay?
If Lord Ferret hadn't shown up, you'd be dead.
About that.
He seemed to know you pretty well.
Of course he does.
We have a deal.
I give him blood, and he gives me whatever I want.
Plus, he serves dinner when I visit.
It might seem wrong to you, but you've got to use your head if you want to survive in this place.
You, wait.
Isn't there anything you want?
Not from you.
I had a feeling I'd find you here.
Why aren't you with Mika?
Did you two have another fight?
That good for nothing?
He's an idiot.
Okay.
Do you want to talk about it?
Just leave me alone.
Don't sit so close.
Why not?
We're family.
It's not weird or anything.
I don't have a family, so it is.
Yes, you do.
Everyone from the Hyakuya Orphanage is one big family.
It's true, because the director said so.
That's stupid.
Attention, everyone.
Yui-jiro here is the newest member of our little family.
So make him feel welcome.
Be on your best behavior, okay?
Okay!
Hey!
Hey, you.
My name's Mikaela.
I'm an orphan, too, so I know how you feel.
I was sad at first, but now I have a big family.
If you like, you can be a part of it.
You think that means anything to me?
You want to know I'm here?
Because my dad went crazy and tried to kill me.
And my mom, she was so convinced that was a demon child that she committed suicide.
You think you know how I feel?
Well, you don't.
Keep your family.
I don't want any part of it.
Wow, that must have been really hard.
But starting today, everything is going to get better.
Well, let's get going.
Dinner's almost ready.
And everyone's waiting on you, Mr. Moody.
Come on, you can be grumpy at the table.
Yuu's home!
Yay, it's time for third!
Careful.
Jeez, you act like I was lost or something.
Guess what?
There's a big surprise in the kitchen.
Akane's making curry with real meat and everything.
Oh, yeah?
Where'd you get all that?
Crazy, isn't it?
I thought I was going to faint when Mika brought it to me.
I'm excited.
I've never had a chance to cook a feast like this before.
What an idiot.
Yummy.
It's so good.
Why aren't you eating anything?
You not hungry?
Oh, yuck, there are carrots in here.
Hey, Akane, guess what?
Today's actually my birthday.
Well, what do you know?
It's my birthday, too.
No fair.
I want one.
I do, too.
I have no choice, then.
I officially declare today everyone's birthday.
For real?
Yay!
Remember to thank Mika whenever he gets home.
Will do!
Why isn't he here for dinner?
Does he not like curry?
Where is Mika?
Do you know you?
Sorry, I don't...
Taichi ate my curry!
Then Taichi can give up the rest of his.
Aw, man!
Why do I know he's getting in trouble?
You stay here for dinner.
you stayed up i'm touched whatever don't tell me you're still angry with me of course not
i ate your curry so we're even huh i'm kidding all the kids really enjoyed it though
so what do you have to do i mean to get the curry
idiot next time we're trading my blood come on nobody wants your nasty blood
kidding forget about it you need to focus on defeating the vampires just leave the rest to
me stop it you can't take on all the burden by yourself i'm not stupid i know how strong the
vampires are i know that beating them is impossible i don't want to hear it these kids look up to you
they hang on your every word we can beat the fangs you won't lose it gives them hope it gives all of
us hope now let's get some grub
here make sure you actually eat this time no it's yours i don't want any too bad
that's not a request it's an order why do i have to take orders from you
because if you don't keep your strength up you won't kill as many fangs with this bad boy
you're not done until you've licked the bowl clean
wow if you think that's impressive check this out
ta-da a map of the city it even shows us where all the exits are
hang on did you steal this from the noble
farid's mansion is as big as a castle it took forever just to find anything useful
the great michaela doesn't give his blood away for a pat on the back
he gets his dues anyway that all stops now we're leaving tonight
i already know what you're gonna say but don't worry i've got it all planned out
just leave it to the great michaela but what about the virus we could die as soon as we get outside
we won't get infected as long as we're 13 or younger remember
any idea how old we are now 12 i think then that gives us a whole year to find a cure
i think we can do it as long as the hyakuya family works together everything will turn out okay
i can't figure out if you really have a plan or if you're just making all this up
i don't know it sounds risky
what are you doing
why are you still awake oh mika hi you ate so what did you think of the curry you
okay mika let's do it great let's go akane go wake everybody up
why
it's time we said goodbye to this city
clear
okay
um
Wow!
Where are we going, anyway?
I don't like the dark.
Won't we get in trouble for being outside?
Don't worry, it's fine.
It won't be long before we're saying bye-bye to this world.
Huh? Why?
I don't get it. Where are we going?
Tell them, Yu.
We're going back to the human world.
And guess what? We can have curry every day.
Really?
I want to have birthday cake every day.
What about hamburger?
Shh.
It looks like we're almost there.
All right, we're in the final stretch.
Let's go.
Yeah.
It looks like we're almost there.
All right, we're in the final stretch.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Oh, hello, little lambs.
I was beginning to wonder if you'd show up.
Aw, just look at those faces.
I love the expression humans make when all of their hopes have been dashed.
It's so intoxicating that I can't stop playing this game.
What game?
What a pity.
Died so quickly.
Damn you!
Well, well.
I believe that is my pistol.
Sneaking it past me took a cunning that few possess.
I'm impressed, Mika.
I never expected to be this entertained.
It makes me hungry for more.
Does that fire of yours need rekindling?
What if I told you that map you stole was the genuine article?
All you have to do is make it past me and you'll be back in your world.
It'll be hard to chase you once you've made it outside.
The question is whether or not you can make it there.
Get going!
Move it!
Yes, that's it.
Go!
We'll hold him off!
I'm begging you.
Leave them alone!
Pakenet, run!
Let me savor the miseries.
You lose everything you hold dear.
It's okay, Yu.
Don't forget.
The two of us, we're family.
Hey!
Sweet, Mikaela.
I'll miss your company most of all.
And the lovely meals.
One...
Two...
Tie.
...
Look at me.
Go, Yu.
Leave me here.
Don't be stupid.
We're going back together, remember?
Don't let us starve for nothing.
Shut up.
You're fine.
You're gonna make it.
Come on.
You're going to make it.
I can't leave.
I can't.
I finally have a family.
I won't lose you.
Just go, you idiot.
And now!
That was the first time we called us family.
Let's go.
Good, he's here.
The prophecy was right.
It was foretold that we would come into contact with one of the test subjects from Hyakuya Labs.
Hey, kid.
How would you like to help us get rid of the vampires once and for all?
I'll do whatever it takes.
As long as I get to kill every last one of them.
I'll do whatever the Viacom
Thank you.
Next time, Seraph of the End.
Humanity after the fall.